<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life Lofranco</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://lifelofranco.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://lifelofranco.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 19:52:57 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 19:52:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Setting things up</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt; Hello World! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Finally! I'm done configuring everything. Setting this site up took a while since I am
still working my way on blogging in Jekyll. I think I am starting to figure out how
everything works, but I'm sure I have a long way until I totally understand everything.
Thankfully, Jekyll's  &lt;!--excerpt--&gt; documentation is easy enough to understand and there are
plenty of resources online. :D
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I've always wanted to start a blog way back, but then life always seems to get in the way. I came
across this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.themacro.com/articles/2016/05/why-the-best-give-away/&quot;&gt; article &lt;/a&gt;
that pushed me to start writing. (You should read it too.) I guess you can say that it was inspiration
that prompted me to start my blog. I just hope this inspiration doesn't go away anytime soon lol.
Also because of my newfound determination, I also bought my first domain today. Funny story when I bought
this domain, my credit card got charged twice. I had to talk with their customer service to ask for a
refund. Haha &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; So what's the purpose of this blog? Well, to document my life of course. I hope I can write just
about everything that matters to me. I am also planning to blog about all
my entreprenurial journeys and write about software and code. Time to share my knowledge to the world. Haha
Since I also easily forget a lot of things, this blog can also serve as my online notes.
I hope I can update this blog continuously! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers! &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 13:40:25 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://lifelofranco.com/getting/started/2016/04/17/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lifelofranco.com/getting/started/2016/04/17/hello-world.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>getting</category>
        
        <category>started</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
